Guide to the Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theater Records, 1934-1994 CTC.1981.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs and Negatives, 1935-1993; III.
  - Individual Performers' Photographs, 1.
    - Frazier, Harry (Box 72, Folder 54)
    - Frasinel, Chester (Box 72, Folder 55)
    - Frederick, J.A. (Box 72, Folder 56)
    - Freedman, Kenneth (Box 72, Folder 57)
    - French, Allan (Box 72, Folder 58)
    - Fretter, Grace (Box 72, Folder 59)
    - Frider, Bob (Box 72, Folder 60)
    - Fuller, Barry (Box 72, Folder 61)
    - Gage, Gary (Box 72, Folder 62)
    - Galarino, Bill (Box 72, Folder 63)
    - Galuppi, Richard (Box 72, Folder 64)
    - Garbrielson, Catherine (Box 72, Folder 65)
    - Gardiner, David (Box 72, Folder 66)
    - Garland, Geoff (Box 72, Folder 67)
    - Garland, Phyllis (Box 72, Folder 68)
    - Gasper, Ed (Box 72, Folder 69)
    - Gaydos, Tom (Box 72, Folder 70)
    - Gellendre, Herbert (Box 72, Folder 71)
    - Georgescu, Ron (Box 72, Folder 72)
    - Geminignani, Rhoda (Box 72, Folder 73)
    - George, Lynn (Box 72, Folder 74)
    - Gill, Robert (Box 72, Folder 75)
    - Gillette, Betty (Box 72, Folder 76)
    - Glenn, Carlotte (Box 72, Folder 77)
    - Glenn, James (Box 72, Folder 78)
    - Glennon, William (Box 72, Folder 79)
    - Gold, Murray (Box 72, Folder 80)
    - Goldfarb, Soralee (Box 72, Folder 81)
    - Goldstein, Harriet (Box 72, Folder 82)
    - Goldstein, Joan (Box 72, Folder 83)
    - Goodman, Ralph (Box 72, Folder 84)
    - Gordon, Judith (Box 72, Folder 85)
    - Gorman, Patrick (Box 72, Folder 86)
    - Goss, Tracy (Box 72, Folder 87)
    - Graham, Richard (Box 72, Folder 88)
    - Gray, Franklin (Box 72, Folder 89)
    - Green, Howard (Box 72, Folder 90)
    - Greene, Gordon (Box 72, Folder 91)
    - Griswold, Mary (Box 72, Folder 92)
    - Gregary, Ruth (Box 72, Folder 93)
    - Grosseck, David (Box 72, Folder 94)
    - Gulak, M. (Box 72, Folder 95)
    - Gwyer, Herbert L. (Box 72, Folder 96)
    - Haddad, Bill (Box 72, Folder 97)
    - Hailey, Marian (Box 72, Folder 98)
    - Haines, Jerrie (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Haines, Mervyn (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Halas, Joseph (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Hall, Ed (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Hamilton, Lynn (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Hamilton, Patricia (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Hamilton, Roger (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Hammer, Mark (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Handcock, John (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Hanson, Arthur (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Hansen, Donna (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Hansen, William (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Hanuck, Jay (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Hanter, Walt (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Hara, Mary (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Harman, Ginger (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Harmon, Kay (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Hatch, Florence (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Hatcher, Christi (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Hauser, Gretchen (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Haydon, Julie (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Hearn, George (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Healy, Mark (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Heinbein, Eileen (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Heiser, Catherine (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Hendle, ? (Conductor) (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Henry, Lee (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Henzie, Martha (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - Herr, Philip K. (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Hettinger, Charles (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Hetzel, William (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Heyman, Barton (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Hickman, Ralph (Box 73, Folder 33)
    - Hild, Donald (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - Hillard, Wanda and Loew, Edith (Box 73, Folder 35)
    - Hoffman, Dean E. (Box 73, Folder 36)
    - Hoffman, Pam (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - Hogue, Robert (Box 73, Folder 38)
    - Hoiby, Lee (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - Holbrook, Hal (Box 73, Folder 40)
    - Hopkins, Cynthia (Box 73, Folder 41)
    - Hops, Harriet (Box 73, Folder 42)
    - Hopper, Mary (Box 73, Folder 43)
    - Hoover, Richard (Box 73, Folder 44)
    - Horn, John (Box 73, Folder 45)
    - Horne, Jim (Box 73, Folder 46)
    - Huffman, David (Box 73, Folder 47)
    - Houde, Ellen (Box 73, Folder 48)
    - Howard, Alison (Box 73, Folder 49)
    - Howard, Celia (Box 73, Folder 50)
    - Howard, Char (Box 73, Folder 51)
    - Howard, Stuart (Box 73, Folder 52)
    - Huggins, Frances Heckert (Box 73, Folder 53)
    - Hughes, Peggy (Box 73, Folder 54)
    - Hugo, Lawrence (Box 73, Folder 55)
    - Hunt, Ed (Box 73, Folder 56)
    - Hurd, Roy (Box 73, Folder 57)
    - Hyman, Elaine (Box 73, Folder 58)
    - Ingleson, Liz (Box 73, Folder 59)
    - Irwin, Sally (Box 73, Folder 60)
    - Itkin, Paul Henry (Box 73, Folder 61)
    - Ivanov, Jorndine (Box 73, Folder 62)
    - Ivery, Dana (Box 73, Folder 63)
    - Jackson, Crane (Box 73, Folder 64)
    - James, Clifton (Box 73, Folder 65)
    - Jarratt, David (Box 73, Folder 66)
    - Jenkins, Esther (Box 73, Folder 67)
    - Jens, Salome (Box 73, Folder 68)
    - Johns, John (Box 73, Folder 69)
    - Johnson, Glenn (Box 73, Folder 70)
    - Johnson, Page (Box 73, Folder 71)
    - Jones, Charlotte (Box 73, Folder 72)
    - Jones, Jane Lloyd (Box 73, Folder 73)
    - Jones, John Bill (Box 73, Folder 74)
    - Jones, Maggie (Box 73, Folder 75)
    - Jordan, Judy (Box 73, Folder 76)
    - Joyce, Florence (Box 73, Folder 77)
    - Jsecks (?), David (Box 73, Folder 78)
    - Julian, Laura (Box 73, Folder 79)
    - Kane, John (Box 73, Folder 80)
    - Kanne, Gretchen (Box 73, Folder 81)
    - Karasevich, Joan (Box 73, Folder 82)
    - Karns, Robert (Box 73, Folder 83)
    - Kasica, Mary Anne (Box 73, Folder 84)
    - Kavanaugh, Richard (Box 73, Folder 85)
    - Keister, Mrs. A.S.F. (Box 73, Folder 86)
    - Kelly, Nancy (Box 73, Folder 87)
    - Kelly, Alice (Box 73, Folder 88)
    - Kenin, Maya (Box 73, Folder 89)
    - Kennedy, James (Box 73, Folder 90)
    - Kent, E. Allen (Box 73, Folder 91)
    - Kent, Deborah (Box 73, Folder 92)
    - Kerns, Milton (Box 73, Folder 93)
    - Kerr, Philip (Box 73, Folder 94)
    - Kerr, Virginia (Box 73, Folder 95)
    - Kessler, Mitch (Box 73, Folder 96)
    - Kettles, Sally (Box 73, Folder 97)
    - Kiliban, Ken (Box 73, Folder 98)
    - Kimbraugh, Charles (Box 73, Folder 99)
    - Kimbraugh, Mary Jane (Box 73, Folder 100)
    - King, Charles (Box 73, Folder 101)
    - King, Princess (Box 73, Folder 102)
    - Kirby, John (Box 73, Folder 103)
    - Kirk, Rachel (Box 73, Folder 104)
    - Klein, Robert (Box 73, Folder 105)
    - Kirk, Lisa (Box 73, Folder 106)
    - Kitch, Ken (Box 73, Folder 107)
    - Kleman, Vic (Box 73, Folder 108)
    - Kletter, Lawrence (Box 73, Folder 109)
    - Knaiz, Judy (Box 73, Folder 110)
    - Knippel, Kathleen (Box 73, Folder 111)
    - Komperda, Edward (Box 73, Folder 112)
    - Korda, Nina (Box 73, Folder 113)
    - Krich, John (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Kubrick, Sylvia (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Kuss, Alice and Richard (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Lacey, Florence (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Lafe, William (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Lagos, Poppy (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Lake, Helen (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Lancaster, Joan (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Lansdale, Keith (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Langworthy, David (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - LaNier, Kitty (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - LaVigne, Robert (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Larson, Orville (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Larson, Richard (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Laurino, Frank (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Law, Jennie Lou (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Lawlor, James Reed (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Lawrence, John (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Layton, Jean (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Lazarus, Pat (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Leberfeld, Alfred (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - LeCocq, Barbara (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Le Roy, Ken (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Lee, Jerry (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Lee, Karen (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Leibowitz, Judith (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Leech, Bill (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - Lehane, Gregory (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Leon, Dorothy (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - Leon, Phyllis (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Lesser, Eugene (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Letchworth, Eileen (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - Levi, Stephen (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - Levin, Shirley (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Levin, Soralee (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Levine, Bob (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - Levine, Dorothy (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - Levine, Milton (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - Lewis, Edward (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - Lewis, Lorna (Box 74, Folder 40)
    - Lewis, Mark (Box 74, Folder 41)
    - Lewis, Marion (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - Lewis, Matthew (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Lewis, Tom (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - Lide, Miller (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - Liggett, Charlene (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - Likar, Charles (Box 74, Folder 47)
    - Lind, Alma (Box 74, Folder 48)
    - Lindgren, Alan (Box 74, Folder 49)
    - Lindig, Anna (Box 74, Folder 50)
    - Link, Robert (Box 74, Folder 51)
    - Linn, David (Box 74, Folder 52)
    - Littel, Patti (Box 74, Folder 53)
    - Loew, Edith (Box 74, Folder 54)
    - Loggia, Robert (Box 74, Folder 55)
    - Lloyd, Christopher (Box 74, Folder 56)
    - Lombard, Rebecca (Box 74, Folder 57)
    - London, Roy (Box 74, Folder 58)
    - Long, Charles (Box 74, Folder 59)
    - Loros, George (Box 74, Folder 60)
    - Lott, Walter (Box 74, Folder 61)
    - Lowry, Jane (Box 74, Folder 62)
    - Luba, Henry (Box 74, Folder 63)
    - Luckinbill, Lawrence (Box 74, Folder 64)
    - Luddeckens, George (Box 74, Folder 65)
    - Lyke, Susanna (Box 74, Folder 66)
    - Lynn, Jeffrey (Box 74, Folder 67)
    - Lyon, Mary (Box 74, Folder 68)
    - Maazel, Lincoln (Box 74, Folder 69)
    - Mabon, Marjorie (Box 74, Folder 70)
    - MacGregor, Scotti (Box 74, Folder 71)
    - MacIntosh, Frank (Box 74, Folder 72)
    - Mack, Edward (Box 74, Folder 73)
    - MacKay, John (Box 74, Folder 74)
    - Macklay, Jean (Box 74, Folder 75)
    - Madia, Dan (Box 74, Folder 76)
    - Maquire, George (Box 74, Folder 77)
    - Maher, Joseph (Box 74, Folder 78)
    - Mamches, Valerie (Box 74, Folder 79)
    - Mangan, Victor (Box 74, Folder 80)
    - Mann, Winifred (Box 74, Folder 81)
    - Manning, Davida (Box 74, Folder 82)
    - Manson, Alan (Box 74, Folder 83)
    - Manwaring, David (Box 74, Folder 84)
    - March, Kendall (Box 74, Folder 85)
    - Margolese, E.M. (Box 74, Folder 86)
    - Margulies, David (Box 74, Folder 87)
    - Marin, Grace (Box 74, Folder 88)
    - Marlatt, Donald (Box 74, Folder 89)
    - Mascarino, Perrino (Box 74, Folder 90)
    - Marks, Bryan (Box 74, Folder 91)
    - Mason, Nan (Box 74, Folder 92)
    - Mathews, Diana (Box 74, Folder 93)
    - Mathews, Anderson (Box 74, Folder 94)
    - Mathews, Bill (Box 74, Folder 95)
    - Mathews, Jacqueline (Box 74, Folder 96)
    - Mayer, Jerry (Box 74, Folder 97)
    - Mayer, Val (Box 74, Folder 98)
    - Mazzioti, Barbara (Box 74, Folder 99)
    - Mazzadro, Gino (Box 74, Folder 100)
    - McAdams, Edward (Box 74, Folder 101)
    - McCabe, Frances (Box 74, Folder 102)
    - McCafferty, George (Box 74, Folder 103)
    - McConn, Marjorie (Box 74, Folder 104)
    - McCandless, Adele (Box 74, Folder 105)
    - McCarthy, Jo Ann (Box 74, Folder 106)
    - McClasky, Glen (Box 74, Folder 107)
    - McCowan, Charles (Box 74, Folder 108)
    - McDonald, Scott (Box 74, Folder 109)
    - McGeorge, Nancy (Box 74, Folder 110)
    - McGroder, Carol (Box 74, Folder 111)
    - McGovern, Terry (Box 74, Folder 112)
    - McKee, Robert (Box 74, Folder 113)
    - McLain, Maryan (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - McLain, Robert (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - McLain, Ted, Jr. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - McLaughlin, Mary (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - McLean, Virginia (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - McMahon, Jere (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - McMillan, Kenneth (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Mears, DeAnn (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Mellor, Douglas (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Meltzer, Joel (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Meredith, Lois (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Merrill, Lonnie (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Metropulos, Penny (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Meyers, Fred (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Michaels, Richard (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Michaels, Stuart (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Mickey, Jerry (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Middleton, Roger (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Mielzinger, Joe (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Milana, Vincent (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Miles, Sylvia (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Miliken, Paul (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Miller, Eugenie (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Miller, Helen (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Miller, Mrs. Henry (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Miller, Michael (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Miller, Raleigh (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Mills, Edmund (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - Mills, Noel (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - Milligan, John (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Milligan, Malcolm (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - Minton, Stephen (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - Mitchell, Grant (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Mitchell, Katherine (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - Mittelman, Arnold (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - Mogck, David (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Montanino. Gennaro (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - Morris, Claude (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - Moses, Philip (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - Moses, Ken (Box 75, Folder 40)
    - Moss, Stephanie (Box 75, Folder 41)
    - Muffly, Ann (Box 75, Folder 42)
    - Muller, James (Box 75, Folder 43)
    - Murphy, Pam (Box 75, Folder 44)
    - Murphy, Patricia (Box 75, Folder 45)
    - Murphy, Richard (Box 75, Folder 46)
    - Napier, Charles (Box 75, Folder 47)
    - Nassif, S. Joseph (Box 75, Folder 48)
    - Negin, Mark (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - Neighbors, George (Box 75, Folder 50)
    - Nellis, Robert (Box 75, Folder 51)
    - Nelley, Clare (Box 75, Folder 52)
    - Nelson, Margot (Box 75, Folder 53)
    - Nelson, Portia (Box 75, Folder 54)
    - Newdick, Dick (Box 75, Folder 55)
    - Nichols, Condo (Box 75, Folder 56)
    - Niles, Richard (Box 75, Folder 57)
    - Nirella, Ruth (Box 75, Folder 58)
    - Noble, James (Box 75, Folder 59)
    - Noble, Sally (Box 75, Folder 60)
    - Norris, Janice (Box 75, Folder 61-61A)
    - Norell, Michael (Box 75, Folder 62)
    - Norris, Lynn (Box 75, Folder 63-64)
    - Norton, Albert (Box 75, Folder 65)
    - Norton, Leonie (Box 75, Folder 66)
    - Nugent, Dana (Box 75, Folder 67)
    - O'Brien, Adale (Box 75, Folder 68)
    - O'Brien, Joseph (Box 75, Folder 69)
    - O'Connell, James (Box 75, Folder 70)
    - O'Connell, Patricia (Box 75, Folder 71)
    - O'Connor, Robert (Box 75, Folder 72)
    - O'Dea, Judy (Box 75, Folder 73)
    - O'Dell, K. Lype (Box 75, Folder 74)
    - Odenz, Leon (Box 75, Folder 75)
    - O'Donnell, Beatrice (Box 75, Folder 76)
    - O'Hanlon, Betty (Box 75, Folder 77)
    - O'Lenick, Carol (Box 75, Folder 78)
    - Oliver, Henry (Box 75, Folder 79)
    - O'Neill, David (Box 75, Folder 80)
    - Omlor, Mary Lou (Box 75, Folder 81)
    - Ornellas, Norman Damien (Box 75, Folder 82)
    - Orwich (?), Barbara (Box 75, Folder 83)
    - Ottenheimer, Albert M. (Box 75, Folder 84)
    - Owens, Barbara (Box 75, Folder 85)
    - Owens, Edwin (Box 75, Folder 86)
    - Palmer, Allison (Box 75, Folder 87)
    - Palmer, Marie Gray (Box 75, Folder 88)
    - Pappas, Steve (Box 75, Folder 89)
    - Parady, Ronald (Box 75, Folder 90)
    - Parks, Robert (Box 75, Folder 91)
    - Parrish, Suzanne (Box 75, Folder 92)
    - Pasquanni, Dini (Box 75, Folder 93)
    - Pasquiri, John (Box 75, Folder 94)
    - Pearce, John (Box 75, Folder 95)
    - Pearlman, Stephen (Box 75, Folder 96)
    - Pelc, Donna (Box 75, Folder 97)
    - Pelles, Victor (Box 75, Folder 98)
    - Pendleton, Briza (Box 75, Folder 99)
    - Pennington, Ann (Box 75, Folder 100)
    - Penrod, Conrad (Box 75, Folder 101)
    - Petterson, Ellen (Box 75, Folder 102)
    - Peyroux, Rip (Box 75, Folder 103)
    - Pezzulo, Ted (Box 75, Folder 104)
    - Phifer, John (Box 75, Folder 105)
    - Pingree, Art (Box 75, Folder 106)
    - Pinsker, Alan (Box 75, Folder 107)
    - Piro, Philip (Box 75, Folder 108)
    - Piscator, Maria Ley (Box 75, Folder 109)
    - Pistilli, Bunny (Box 75, Folder 110)
    - Pistilli, Carl (Box 75, Folder 111)
    - Pivirotti, Ruth (Box 75, Folder 112)
    - Plumley, Donald (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Pochapin, Martin (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Ponzini, Anthony (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Porter, Earl (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Porter, Norman (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Prendergast, James (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Prince, Bob (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Pross, Jules (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Putch, William (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Rachine, Alan (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Ragan, James (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Rand, Jamie (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Rauh, Helen Wayne (Box 76, Folder 13-14)
    - Rauh, Richard (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Ray, Gene (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Ray, Mary Ellen (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Reed, Jason (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Reed, John (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Regan, Charles (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Reily, George W. (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Reinholt, George (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Reisberg, Dorothy (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Reisman, ? [Female] (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Remmey, John (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Reynolds, Jonathan (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Reynolds, Pauline (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Rice, Patricia (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Richards, Del (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Richard, Gerald (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Richards, Lisa (Box 76, Folder 31)
    - Ricks, Ginny (Box 76, Folder 32)
    - Riddle, Gladys (Box 76, Folder 33)
    - Riehl, Donald (Box 76, Folder 34)
    - Reinhardt, Ray (Box 76, Folder 35)
    - Riseman, Naomi (Box 76, Folder 36)
    - Roberts, Art (Box 76, Folder 37)
    - Roberts, Arthur (Box 76, Folder 38)
    - Roberts, William (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - Robin, Naomi (Box 76, Folder 40)
    - Robinson, Hal (Box 76, Folder 41)
    - Roe, Charles (Box 76, Folder 42)
    - Roland, George (Box 76, Folder 43)
    - Rosen, Irene (Box 76, Folder 44)
    - Rosenberg, Harriet (Box 76, Folder 45)
    - Rosoff, Muriel (Box 76, Folder 46)
    - Ross, William (Box 76, Folder 47)
    - Rossen, Carol (Box 76, Folder 48)
    - Roth, Adelyne (Box 76, Folder 49)
    - Roth, Audrey (Box 76, Folder 50)
    - Roussel, Elsa (Box 76, Folder 51)
    - Roudabus, Marcia (Box 76, Folder 52)
    - Rowles, Polly (Box 76, Folder 53)
    - Rubbo, Kathy (Box 76, Folder 54)
    - Rubinstein, Arthur (Box 76, Folder 55)
    - Rubinstein, Carol (Box 76, Folder 56)
    - Ruisinger, Thomas (Box 76, Folder 57)
    - Ryan, William (Box 76, Folder 58)
    - Safranek, Penny (Box 76, Folder 59)
    - Salin, Harvey (Box 76, Folder 60)
    - Sanderson, Septa (Box 76, Folder 61)
    - Sando, Florence (Box 76, Folder 62)
    - Satlof, Ronald (Box 76, Folder 63)
    - Savage, Ramona (Box 76, Folder 64)
    - Scarnecchia, Sally (Box 76, Folder 65)
    - Schacht, Sam (Box 76, Folder 66)
    - Schad, Joe (Box 76, Folder 67)
    - Schelling, Roberta (Box 76, Folder 68)
    - Schmidtke, Ned (Box 76, Folder 69)
    - Schmitt, Jamie (Box 76, Folder 70)
    - Schneider, ? [female] (Box 76, Folder 71)
    - Schwartz, Sam (Box 76, Folder 72)
    - Scott, David (Box 76, Folder 73)
    - Scott, Dorothy (Box 76, Folder 74)
    - Scott, Herald (Box 76, Folder 75)
    - Scott, Marc (Box 76, Folder 76)
    - Scott, Stephen (Box 76, Folder 77)
    - Scovel, Charles (Box 76, Folder 78)
    - Seibert, Charles (Box 76, Folder 79)
    - Seitz, John F. (Box 76, Folder 80)
    - Selman, Linda (Box 76, Folder 81)
    - Serlin, Sol (Box 76, Folder 82)
    - Shaffner, Nancy (Box 76, Folder 83)
    - Sharpe, Clyde (Box 76, Folder 84)
    - Shaw, Leon (Box 76, Folder 85)
    - Shaw, Margery (Box 76, Folder 86)
    - Shaw, Stephen (Box 76, Folder 87)
    - Shea, Norma Jane (Box 76, Folder 88)
    - Shenar, Paul (Box 76, Folder 89)
    - Shenken, Joe (Box 76, Folder 90)
    - Shephard, Joan (Box 76, Folder 91)
    - Shirvan, Harriet (Box 76, Folder 92)
    - Siebert, Charles (Box 76, Folder 93)
    - Segaloff, Eve (Box 76, Folder 94)
    - Siler, Cinda (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Siletti, Mario (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Sillett, Frederick (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Simmons, Pat (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Simpson, Barry (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Singer, Laura (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Sivy, Michael (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Skelly, Kay (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Skelton, William (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Skinner, Edith (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Sklai, Mike (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Smiley, Robert (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Alfred E. (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Barbara (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Ivan (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Smith, J. English (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Sharon Louise (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - Smith, William (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - Snyder, Frank (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - Snyder, Richard (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - Soggi, Marian (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - Solin, Harvey (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - Sorel, Theodore (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Sortino, Doug (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Sowash, Jeffrey (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - Spencer, Janel (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - Spandelman, Bruno (Box 77, Folder 27)
    - Stackrath, David (Box 77, Folder 28)
    - Stainback, Anne (Box 77, Folder 29)
    - Stamos, Nichols (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Starkweather, John (Box 77, Folder 31)
    - Staw, Sala (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Steen, Courtland (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Steibl, Trudy (Box 77, Folder 34)
    - Steinfeld, Edward (Box 77, Folder 35)
    - Steiner, Mitzi (Box 77, Folder 36)
    - Sterba, Josephine (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Sterling, Jan (Box 77, Folder 38)
    - Stevens, Julie (Box 77, Folder 39)
    - Stevens, Leon B. (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - Stevenson, ? [male] (Box 77, Folder 41)
    - Stevlingson, Edward (Box 77, Folder 42)
    - Stewart, Patricia (Box 77, Folder 43)
    - Stiefel, Beth (Box 77, Folder 44)
    - Stohl, Hank (Box 77, Folder 45)
    - Stoller, Ira (Box 77, Folder 46)
    - Stone, Harold (Box 77, Folder 47)
    - Stone, Sandia (Box 77, Folder 48)
    - Stough, Ray (Box 77, Folder 49)
    - Stout, Helen (Box 77, Folder 50)
    - Strang, Frank (Box 77, Folder 51)
    - Strasberg, Anna (Box 77, Folder 52)
    - Strasberg, Lee (Box 77, Folder 53)
    - Strasser, Robin (Box 77, Folder 54)
    - Strassler, Jack (Box 77, Folder 55)
    - Strasun, Gabrielle (Box 77, Folder 56)
    - Struthers, Thomas (Box 77, Folder 57)
    - Sufrin, Ben (Box 77, Folder 58)
    - Sullivan, Kitty (Box 77, Folder 59)
    - Tabor, Bill (Box 77, Folder 60)
    - Talenfield, Leonard (Box 77, Folder 61)
    - Tarpey, Thomas (Box 77, Folder 62)
    - Tashjian, Vahan (Box 77, Folder 63)
    - Tate, Edmond (Box 77, Folder 64)
    - Tatistcheff, Peter (Box 77, Folder 65)
    - Tavares, Eric (Box 77, Folder 66)
    - Taylor, Eugene (Box 77, Folder 67)
    - Teitel, Carol (Box 77, Folder 68)
    - Thomas, Henry (Box 77, Folder 69)
    - Tompkins, David (Box 77, Folder 70)
    - Thompson, Anne (Box 77, Folder 71)
    - Thompson, Evan (Box 77, Folder 72)
    - Thompson, Larry (Box 77, Folder 73)
    - Thompson, Richard (Box 77, Folder 74)
    - Thunhurst, William (Box 77, Folder 75)
    - Thurner, James (Box 77, Folder 76)
    - Tobin, Marvin (Box 77, Folder 77)
    - Toldi, Eda (Box 77, Folder 78)
    - Touzly, Mary (Box 77, Folder 79)
    - Towey, John (Box 77, Folder 80)
    - Trapp, Deborah (Box 77, Folder 81)
    - Trent, John (Box 77, Folder 82)
    - Treon, Katie (Box 77, Folder 83)
    - Tildi, Edu (Box 77, Folder 84)
    - Turner, Terence (Box 77, Folder 85)
    - Turney, Harold (Box 77, Folder 86)
    - Turton, Patricia (Box 77, Folder 87)
    - Tyson, Cicely (Box 77, Folder 88)
    - Ulmer, John (Box 77, Folder 89)
    - Ungerer, Corinne (Box 77, Folder 90)
    - Valentine, John (Box 77, Folder 91)
    - Van Duser, Jane (Box 77, Folder 92)
    - Varela, Nina (Box 77, Folder 93)
    - Varnay, David (Box 77, Folder 94)
    - Vaughn, Rees (Box 77, Folder 95)
    - Vereska, Valerie (Box 77, Folder 96)
    - Viehman, Theodore (Box 77, Folder 97)
    - Vigoda, Abe (Box 77, Folder 98)
    - Valskamp, Jacqueline (Box 77, Folder 99)
    - Vogel, Jack (Box 77, Folder 100)
    - Waalewijn, Mies (Box 77, Folder 101)
    - Walker, Dolores (Box 77, Folder 102)
    - Wallace, Lee (Box 77, Folder 103)